{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I say 'meow' and like to chase string. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk."},{"text":"🧶 I like to play with yarn."},{"text":"🐈‍⬛ Some people keep me as a pet."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I bark and wag my tail. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I love to chew on bones."},{"text":"🎾 I like to play fetch."},{"text":"🏡 I protect your house."}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I say 'quack' and swim in a pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌾 I eat weeds and seeds."},{"text":"🧡 Some are yellow and fluffy when they are babies."},{"text":"💦 I like to swim in water."}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Chicken","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I give you milk and say 'moo'. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌱 I eat grass in a field."},{"text":"🥛 You drink my milk."},{"text":"⚫ I have black and white spots."}],"options":[{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Goat","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥜 I love to eat peanuts."},{"text":"🐘 I am very big."},{"text":"💧 I can spray water with my nose."}],"options":[{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I hop around and eat carrots. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I love to eat orange things."},{"text":"🐰 I have long ears."},{"text":"🌱 I like to eat vegetables from the ground"}],"options":[{"label":"Turtle","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Squirrel","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I am the king of the jungle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦁 I have a big mane."},{"text":"☀️ I live in Africa."},{"text":"🐾 I'm a very big cat."}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Wolf","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I have black and white stripes. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐴 I look a bit like a horse."},{"text":"🦓 I live in Africa."},{"text":"🦓 I eat grass and leaves."}],"options":[{"label":"Zebra","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Panda","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cheetah","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I fly at night and say 'hoot'. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦉 I have big eyes."},{"text":"🌙 I sleep during the day."},{"text":"🌲 I live in a tree."}],"options":[{"label":"Eagle","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Owl","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Robin","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I climb trees and eat bananas. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐒 I like to swing from branches."},{"text":"🍌 I peel and eat yellow fruit."},{"text":"🌴 I live in the jungle."}],"options":[{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sloth","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Koala","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}],"weather":[{"level":"1","type":"weather","question":"I fall from the sky, and you need an umbrella. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💧 I'm wet!"},{"text":"🌧️ I come from clouds."},{"text":"☔ I make puddles."}],"options":[{"label":"Rain","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sun","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Stars","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"2","type":"weather","question":"I am big and bright and hot. I shine in the day. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"☀️ I make you warm."},{"text":"😎 You need sunglasses when I'm out."},{"text":"💛 I am very yellow."}],"options":[{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sun","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cloud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"3","type":"weather","question":"I am white and fluffy and float in the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐑 I look like a sheep sometimes."},{"text":"✈️ Airplanes fly through me."},{"text":"🌫️ I can block the sun."}],"options":[{"label":"Cloud","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Tree","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Car","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"4","type":"weather","question":"I am cold and white, and I fall from the sky in winter. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"❄️ I am very cold."},{"text":"⛄ You can make a snowman with me."},{"text":"🧤 You need gloves when I'm around."}],"options":[{"label":"Snow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Leaves","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Mud","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"5","type":"weather","question":"I am a big storm with lots of wind and rain. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💨 I can blow your hat off."},{"text":"⚡ Sometimes I have lightning."},{"text":"🏡 It's best to stay inside when I visit."}],"options":[{"label":"Party","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Storm","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Picnic","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"6","type":"weather","question":"I am very strong wind. I can make the leaves fly around. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍃 I make things move."},{"text":"🪁 You can fly a kite when I'm blowing."},{"text":"🌬️ You can feel me, but not see me."}],"options":[{"label":"Fire","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Wind","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Water","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"7","type":"weather","question":"Sometimes after the rain, you can see me with many colors in the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌈 I have red, orange, yellow, green, blue, indigo and violet."},{"text":"☀️ I appear when the sun shines through the rain."},{"text":"✨ I look like a colorful arc."}],"options":[{"label":"Rainbow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Stars","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Puddle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"8","type":"weather","question":"I am small frozen raindrops, sometimes I fall during a storm. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧊 I am cold and hard"},{"text":"🤕 Sometimes, I hurt if I hit you"},{"text":"⚾ I am smaller than a baseball."}],"options":[{"label":"Clouds","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Hail","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rain","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"9","type":"weather","question":"I am a cloud that touches the ground, making it hard to see. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌫️ I'm like a cloud on the ground."},{"text":"🚗 You have to drive slowly when I'm around."},{"text":"👻 I can make things disappear."}],"options":[{"label":"Snow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sun","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}},{"level":"10","type":"weather","question":"Sometimes when it's very hot, I can appear as shimmering water on the road, but it's not really there. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🔥 I happen when it is really hot."},{"text":"😵‍💫 You're eyes are playing tricks on you"},{"text":"🏜️ You might see me in a desert."}],"options":[{"label":"Mirage","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Puddle","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lake","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"🌦️"}}]}